

 \searrow

mailtojustinj@gmail.com

09633948375



bethel, charuvilakam, thiruvananthapuram, India



05 August, 1993



justinjj16.github.io/justinjosep

in

linkedin.com/in/justinjj16



github.com/justinjj16



stackoverflow.com/story/justinjj08

SKILLS

JavaScript

React

Angular

Graphal

Node js

AWS

Skill

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Malayalam

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

fitness

Golf

Justin Joseph

Software Engineer

Experienced Software Engineer with demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in JavaScript, React, Angular, node js, Redux-saga, cloud functions. Strong engineering professional with a Master (MSc) focused in Computer Science from Mahatma Gandhi University

WORK EXPERIENCE

React, JavaScript, Angular, Graphql, AWS Neoito

09/2019 - Present Thiruvananthapuram

JavaScript

Adhoc Technologies

07/2018 - 09/2019 Thiruvananthapuram

EDUCATION

MSc Computer Science

College of Applied Science, payyappady

09/2014 - 07/2016 61%

BSc Computer Science

NMCC, Marthandam

07/2011 - 06/2014 64%

Higher Secondary

Concordia Lutheran Higher Secondary School

06/2009 - 05/2011 63%

Secondary School

Government Model Boys Higher Secondary School

06/2009 70%